ADDY OSMANI: Hello.
你好
I'm Addy Osmani.
我是Addy Osmani。
MATT GAUNT: And I'm Matt Gaunt.
我是Matt Gaunt。
ADDY OSMANI: OK.
知道了
So WebPagetest is this great tool
WebPagetest是一个很棒的工具
for testing the performance of your site
测试您网站的性能
from multiple locations around the world.
来自世界各地。
We use it a lot when we're building progressive web
我们经常使用它们，我们正在建造
apps at the moment.
脱机Web应用程序脱机。
So this is like the interface-to-web page test.
这类似于测试基于Web的用户界面。
The basic idea is you just go in and you fill out the site
主要思想是您只需注册
that you want to test out.
您要测试的站点的名称。
What we usually do is we go to Advanced Settings
我们通常要做的是进行高级设置
and we, first of all, set the number of tests
最初，我们调整测试数量
to run because these can vary, because WebPagetest often
之所以这样做，是因为它可以变化，因为WebPagetest通常
runs on actual devices.
适用于真实设备。
And you can set the location that you want
您可以在所需的地方设置
to test from around the world.
有来自世界各地的测试。
We set three, so that you get a relatively decent set
我们设置三个，您将获得一个结果集
of different pieces of data.
具有比例数据。
And it's just going to average them out for you.
它会给你平均分。
So when you go in and you run your test,
因此，当您开始测试时
it's going to look a little bit like this.
看起来有点像这样。
So this is testing Paul Lewis's Voice Memos app out.
这是Paul Lewis语音笔记的测试应用程序。
And you get this nice, little table
你会发现这张小桌子
at the very top that's got data like load time, start
它的顶部包含加载时间和开始投放等数据
render, and the speed index.
和速度指示器。
Matt, what's the Speed Index?
Matt什么是速度指示器？
MATT GAUNT: I believe the Speed Index is basically
我认为主要是
the visual completeness of the page relative to all
根据每个页面的视觉形状，页面的完整性
the pages on the internet.
在线页面。
ADDY OSMANI: You are right, sir.
是的，先生。
You are right.
没错
And the index also includes the timeline breakdown
速度指示器还包括时间表详细信息
and screenshots, just showing you all that nice stuff.
对于截图，我将向您展示美好的事物。
But for Speed Index, you basically
对于速度指示器，
want to try getting, for at least cable, as close to 1,000
基本上，您至少应尝试使用1000条电缆
as possible.
如果可能的话。
And if you're targeting, like, 3G,
例如，如果您要定位3G，
you're looking at maybe around 3,000.
因此，您需要大约3,000。
MATT GAUNT: And I'd also argue, on the Repeat View,
我还要提及重复报价
you should basically be getting as close to zero as humanly
您必须使其接近零
possible.
尽可能地。
Repeat View is basically like the page,
重复宽度就像一页，
everything's loaded once, everything
放置后一切都会加载
should be in the cache.
在临时内存中。
So you should literally be pulling everything
所以你真的把一切都拉了
from the HTTP cache, and it should be super fast.
HTTP缓存，而且很快。
ADDY OSMANI: And in this case, Paul Lewis
在这种情况下，保罗·刘易斯
was using Service Worker.
它使用服务器代理。
So you'll see that he's getting a pretty decent Speed
所以你看到他有一个出色的速度指示器
Index, which is good.
很好
So just try to get that as low down as possible.
因此，您可以尽可能减少这种情况。
When you're in your Advanced Settings page,
在“高级设置”页面上时，
you'll also notice that there's a section called Connection.
您会注意到一个名为Connection的部分。
Because a lot of the time, your users
因为通常，您的用户
might be on the go-- they might be on the train
他们可能很着急-也许正在火车上
or running away from the cops or something,
或逃避警察之类的
I don't know-- you should probably
我不知道-你要么
also try out the 3G settings and see
也许会体验3G设置并查看
how well you're doing there.
你如何领导它。
So just select Mobile 3G, go and run your test again.
只需选择Mobile 3G，然后再次进行测试。
And that will look a little bit like this.
这看起来像这样。
So very similar to the page we had before.
与我们之前获得的页面非常相似。
You'll notice that the Speed Index score has now changed.
您会注意到速度指示器结果已更改。
So this is still under 3,000.
少于3,000。
It's doing pretty well.
很好
Speed Index for Repeat View has also gone up.
显示速度指示器的频率也上升。
It should probably be a little bit lower.
你应该少一点。
MATT GAUNT: I think it's nice, basically,
我认为那很美
to get something that is out of your control.
要得到你无法控制的东西。
I think that's the main reason why
我认为这是主要原因
I use this is it's something like my environment
如此使用它就像一个特殊的环境
where I'm running these tests can't be affected.
这些测试不受影响。
It's just WebPagetest is an independent party.
WebPagetest是独立的。
So it's good.
那很好
ADDY OSMANI: It's good.
真的很好
It's solid.
而且稳定。
So another thing that we usually check
我们通常会遇到的另一件事
is the Capture Video option.
是选择视频拍摄。
So Capture Video is also in Advanced Settings.
这也在高级设置中。
Just capture-- start the test.
只需快速启动测试。
And when you do that, you'll get this video.
然后，您将获得此视频。
So on that tab that we were on before,
在此标签中，我们以前是
you'll notice that there's this little link called
您会注意到该小链接及其名称
Filmstrip View.
幻灯片视图。
Click that.
按下
And it'll actually give you a filmstrip showing you
该视频将向您详细介绍出现的位置
all of the frames that were captured over time.
随时间推移已记录的所有轮胎。
And this is super useful for actually getting to see things
这对于了解事情的进展非常有用
like first meaningful paint.
就像看到带有图形的第一帧一样。
So here, we can see it around two seconds.
在这里我们可以看到大约两秒钟。
We actually got some of the top toolbar being drawn
上方的工具栏也显示为
and the material design fab icon.
和材料设计图标。
We have some text.
我们有一些文字。
We've got a loader showing.
并在此处显示下载图标。
And you can see the progression, three, two.
您会看到进度，一，二。
I would say four seconds is about when
大约四秒钟
you get your proper first meaningful paint in place.
您将获得第一笔有用的费用。
Some members of the Chrome team say
一些Chrome小组成员说
first meaningful paint is when you've got actual text showing
具有有用图形的第一帧是当您使实际文本出现时
up on the screen.
在屏幕顶部。
So four seconds is how long that took.
所以花了四秒钟。
And this is 3G as well.
那也是3G。
Paul always does really well on the cable scores
保罗在电缆方面表现出色
for this stuff.
对于这些东西。
You can also get a video view.
您还可以获取视频演示。
So remember, we captured video.
所以请记住，我们拍了一个视频。
If we go to the Video View here, you can actually see,
如果我们在这里观看视频，您可以看到，
OK, well, all these frames are playing back,
好吧，所有这些帧都显示出来了，
and it shows you the progression [INAUDIBLE].
演示中显示了进度。
You have four seconds until we've actually
你甚至有四秒钟
got visual completeness.
您将获得完整的视野。
So that's useful as well.
这也是有用的。
Back on WebPagetest.
我们指的是WebPagetest。
If you go to Chrome-- so there's a dedicated Chrome tab
如果您使用的是Chrome浏览器-有一个自定义标签
here with a few extra options in there.
这里还有其他选择。
One of them is Capture DevTools Timeline.
一种是Capture DevTools计划。
Now, if you check that and you go and you do a recording,
现在，如果您检查它并去注册，
you'll actually get this little Timeline option
您将选择一个直播时间表
in the very left in a column.
一列中最左侧。
You can download a Chrome DevTools timeline there.
您可以在此处下载Chrome DevTools时间表。
And then you can open up-- in DevTools,
然后，您可以在DevTools中打开，
you can just go to your Timeline View, load the JSON file,
您可以查看时间表，下载JSON文件，
and load that in there.
并在那里上传。
You can also just click View, and it'll
您也可以点击查看，它将
show you that timeline in a tab.
时间表显示在选项卡中。
There's another tab on WebPagetest here called
WebPagetest中还有另一个选项卡称为
Visual Comparison.
视觉比较。
Now, this is super useful for-- like,
这非常有用-例如
let's say you've got some assumptions
你有一些假设
you want to check out, like you've got a new UI that you
您要检查的内容，例如您有一个新的UI
want to ship, and you want to see
你想移动，你想看
how well it compares performance-wise
如何比较效果
to your old one.
对于老。
Or like, you want to see what the impact of ads
或者，例如，您想查看广告的效果是什么
are on your page and stuff like that.
在您的页面或类似的内容上。
MATT GAUNT: Like, it's good if you had staging versus release,
很好的例子，如果您使用的是平台版本，
and you've done a lot of performance work.
而且您需要做很多工作来提高性能
You want to make sure that you are actually doing well.
您想确保自己做得很好。
ADDY OSMANI: Because I'm a jerk, I'm
因为我很傻
just going to use this to compare
我将用它来比较
the performance of some of the apps
一些应用程序的性能
our team have been building.
我们的团队正在建设。
And it looks a little bit like this.
他们看起来有点像这样。
So I've got Paul Lewis, Jake, Kinlan, and me.
所以我有Paul Lewis，Jake，Kinlan和我。
And you can see the progression of visual completeness here.
可以看到视觉完整性的进展。
Half a second, we still have a white screen.
半秒钟，我们仍然有一个白色的屏幕。
Then around 0.7, oh, look, Jake's got some content.
在0.7的外观下，杰克出现了一些内容
And poor Kinlan's [INAUDIBLE], which basically has nothing,
而Kinlan的少量内容却一无所获，
but it's the fastest thing there is there.
但这是目前为止最快的事情。
MATT GAUNT: I do like how it loads,
我喜欢它的加载方式
and then it's just like, done.
突然结束了，完成了。
ADDY OSMANI: But you can see the progression.
但是您可以看到进度。
Like around one second, I've actually got some content here.
大约一秒钟，我在这里有一些内容。
Jake's already got all his text and everything going.
杰克已经拥有全文和其余内容。
I think he's using streams and other--
我认为他使用流量，并且-
MATT GAUNT: You had to say it, didn't you?
你应该这么说的，不是吗？
ADDY OSMANI: Streams!
流！
Streams and other magic.
流动和一些魔术。
And this is just really nice for being
这很漂亮，因为您可以
able to compare visual completeness
能够比较视觉完整性
across a few different builds of things.
在几种不同版本的事物之间。
Another option on WebPagetest under Advanced
在高级设置中选择另一个WebPagetest
is the ability to disable JavaScript, which is useful
是禁用JavaScript的功能，非常有用
if you want to check out the impact
如果要检查效果
of third-party resources, and ads, and stuff like that.
那是由第三方，广告之类的东西留下的。
MATT GAUNT: But it's also useful if you just
如果需要的话也很有用
want to see what happens if you're in a browser where--
您可以在浏览器中看到以下情况，
let's say, hypothetically, your JavaScript failed, and you
假设默认情况下，您的JavaScript失败了
were relying on it heavily.
而你严重依赖他。
You could find out.
你知道的
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的
And if you need even more granular control
如果您需要控制在较低水平
over this type of thing, you can also
除了这个东西，你也可以
block requests to specific resources
阻止对特定来源的请求
over in the Block tab.
在[封锁]标签中
You talked about test history.
我谈到了考试历史。
So I had no idea that this was a thing.
我不知道有这样的事情。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
So I think what I was doing was I was changing my website,
我认为我正在做的是改变我的立场，
and I actually wanted to retroactively compare
回顾性的，我想比较一下
new and old runs of my site.
在我的网站的新旧运行之间。
And it turns out WebPagetest actually
显示该WebPagetest
logs a lot of this information.
存储大量的信息。
So you can literally select runs from the past year
您可以从字面上选择去年的跑步
from any user that's just stuffed your site
来自进入您网站的任何用户
through WebPagetest and actually get access
通过WebPagetest并访问结果
to those test results.
测试那些。
So if you wanted to compare really old builds versus new,
因此，如果您要将旧版本与新版本进行比较，
you can totally do that through WebPagetest.
您可以通过WebPagetest执行此操作。
It's all just there, which is awesome.
就在这里，太棒了。
ADDY OSMANI: One last thing.
最后一件事。
This is something I only recently discovered.
这是我最近发现的。
So WebPagetest also has this JPEG Info tool.
WebPagetest具有JPEG格式的信息工具。
So webpagetest.org/jpeginfo.
webpagetest.org/jpeginfo。
You can just add in a URL to any image here and analyze it.
您只能添加要分析的任何图像的URL。
And what it'll actually do is it'll show you
我会跋涉
what compression savings you can get
压缩后如何存储容量
by going for lossless compression
通过按下，不会浪费数据
or changing up the image quality to something
或更改图像质量
a little bit different to what you've got right now, like size
与您现在所拥有的不同，例如尺寸
85, in this case, which is still saving you
85，在这种情况下，他们仍然提供
bytes on the original 140K image.
容量而不是最初的14万。
But it's just a nice, little, extra thing WebPagetest does.
这是WebPagetest要做的一件好事。
Not a lot of people use this, like, know this tool exists.
使用它们的人并不多，不了解它们。
But it's kind of neat.
一个相当不错的工具。
MATT GAUNT: No, it's pretty cool,
不，真的很棒
because it also gives you a score of image compression
它给您的图像压缩等级
on your runs and everything.
每次您运行等等。
So it's nice to be able to do that.
您可以做到这一点很好。
ADDY OSMANI: There's a ton of other options
有很多不同的选择
WebPagetest have got.
在WebPagetest中。
You can keep your tests private, set labels.
您可以对测试保密，并为其命名。
You can set custom user timings.
您可以设置自定义用户计时。
So if visual completeness requires better markings up
因此，如果视觉完整性需要更好的准备
in the Waterfall view that they've got,
在瀑布视图中
you can check that stuff out.
你会失去那些东西。
Supports authentication and a ton of other stuff.
支持身份验证和很多东西。
So WebPagetest is awesome.
WebPagetest很棒。
Go check it out.
只是去失去他。
MATT GAUNT: Yes, use it every day.
是的，每天使用。